Hello .
Is that Alice ?
No , I think you 've got the wrong number .
Well , what 's your name ?
This is Stacy .
Wh ... ? Who is this ?
Hello .
Who is this ?
Hey , Mr. Wilson . - Hey , Dennis .
A.J. Charlie . Katherine .
A.J.
Charlie .
Andrew Joseph .
A.J.
Charlie ? Katherine .
Hello .
Please stop calling me .
Wait . Let 's see it .
I 'm winning you . - Come on , you guys .
Hello , sir .
We have a 44-year-old white female ...
What 's going on ?
We were patrolling a block away when the call came .
Who made the call ? - I 'm not sure , sir .
Well , where did you find them ? - Upstairs bedroom .
Hey , Harv . - Hey , Hines . You 're growing a beard .
Yes , I am . - Makes you look ...
Old and fat . I know , I 've heard .
Where am I going , Lewis ? - Just around here , sir .
What did the coroner say ? - He 's still here , wading through it all .
Wading through it all ?
You need gloves , sir ? - Yeah . Give them to me .
That 's a bedroom round to your left .
What was the murder weapon ? - That 's just it .
What ?
There wasn 't one .
Nice , nice . Come on , get that .
Sorry , coach .
You 're not concentrating , Jill .
You can make 24 seconds . We both know you can .
Just focus on something in the distance , and then ...
Run for it like nothing else exists .
Right .
Okay . Good practice , ladies . Hit the showers .
Hey , Jill . - Hey , Boom Boom .
I 'm sorry , your service has been temporarily interrupted .
If this is an emergency , please dial 911 .
Jill .
Come on , Jill . You just gonna ignore me forever ?
Sounds good to me .
I tried to call you last night , but your cell phone was tweaked .
We need to talk . - Bobby , we 've talked .
Seventy-four minutes yesterday , 124 the day before
and 256 the day before that .
Just hear me out . - I saw you with her .
Well , what else is there to discuss ?
She kissed me . I keep telling you that .
I barely even remember it , anyway . - Wait , so you let her kiss you .
Please ... - Later , Bobby .
Am I gonna see you tonight ?
Did you hang tough ? - I hung .
I don 't want you giving in to those blue eyes .
I 'm not gonna give in .
You know , that 's just the worst lion I 've ever seen , I gotta tell you .
It 's ... I know .
So , what time are you picking us up tonight ?
I 'm not picking anyone up .
What do you mean ? - I 'm grounded .
All because you went over your minutes ?
Yep . Thanks to that jerk . - I thought they were gonna wait
till after the bonfire . - So did I.
Hey , guys .
Guys , this is so high school . - Scarlet , we 're in high school .
Anyway , they 're making me pay it off .
Yeah , I have to babysit . Tonight . - Tonight ?
Who needs some stupid bonfire party , anyway ?
It 's just a bunch of skanks and jerks acting like idiots , right ?
So Mom was able to get the tickets .
I was kind of hoping they 'd be sold-out .
Just be glad you 're not going .
It 's baroque chamber music .
Since the concert isn 't over until after midnight
Dr. Mandrakis will drive you home , okay ?
I could have at least driven myself , Dad .
Jill , you went over by 800 minutes .
Do you know how much that cost us ?
At least you could wait until after 8 : 00 . - I know .
I always do . - Except this time you didn 't .
That 's ... That 's not fair , Dad . You know why .
Sweetheart , I know . But still ...
Wha ? So if I drove myself , you think I 'd have just bailed and not shown up ?
It 's one month , Jill . No phone , no car .
Besides , I don 't want you driving home alone this far so late at night .
Boy
they really live pretty far out here . - Yep .
You gonna be okay out here alone ? - Depends what they have TiVo-ed .
Guess I should have been a doctor .
Just think of this as learning responsibility .
Dad , I am responsible .
I mean , when it 's not easy
when it 's complicated , when it hurts . That 's when it counts .
Call us if you need anything .
You guys have fun . - Say it like you mean it .
Hi , I 'm the babysitter .
Oh , right , yes . Come in .
I 'm sorry to rush , but I think we 're a little late .
Honey , have you seen the keys ?
Don 't yell . I just got the kids to sleep .
Did you check the kitchen ? - Yeah .
Well , try the office .
You must be Jill . I 'm Kelly Mandrakis .
Nice to meet you both .
We were so thrilled to find a babysitter at the last minute .
You come highly recommended by the Thompsons .
Well , they 're great .
If you can handle them , we 're gonna be a cakewalk .
Yeah .
Tim , keys ? - Yeah .
Come on , I 'll show you around .
The kitchen 's back here .
That 's Chester . He 'll probably be there all night .
It 's beautiful .
Bye , Chester .
Oh , you 'll get used to that .
Here 's a list of all the contact and emergency numbers you might need .
Our cell numbers . And that 's the number of the restaurant .
Here 's the phone . Don 't hesitate to call us about anything .
Oh , and help yourself to anything in the fridge .
I remember babysitting . Food 's the best part .
Oh , and if you hear any banging around upstairs , don 't worry .
That 's our live-in Rosa . She has a room on the third floor .
She sometimes leaves to go take care of her mother
who 's been pretty sick recently .
Your house is amazing . - Thank you .
Tim , have you seen my ?
Okay . Anything else , or are we done ?
The guesthouse ? - Guesthouse .
Our son , who 's in college , stays out there most weekends .
Not that he ever calls to let us know when he 's coming .
You have a son in college ?
From my first marriage .
Our dinner reservations are at 8
but we might catch a movie afterwards
which would put us home around midnight . Is that okay ?
That 's fine . - Great .
Okay . Anything else ? All set ? - The children ?
First bedroom at the top of the landing .
They 're getting over the flu .
We had a hard time getting them to sleep
so whatever you do , please , try not to wake them .
Oh , we have an alarm system .
I 'll write the code down for you right here .
You familiar with these ? - Yes .
Okay , honey , let 's go .
Bye .
Just make yourself at home . - Okay .
Oh , thank you . I just bought them .
Hello ?
Dr. Mandrakis ?
Rosa ?
Rosa , this is Jill the babysitter .
Hello .
Mandrakis residence .
Hello ?
Chester .
What are the kids like ?
I don 't know . They were asleep when I got here .
And the house ?
Pretty amazing .
You should see her closet . It 's bigger than my room .
Food ?
I haven 't checked that out yet .
Good closet means good supplies .
Listen , I 'm not sure if I should tell you this , but ...
What ?
The jerk called me .
He wants your number over there .
Well , did you give it to him ?
No , because he 'd call .
It 's okay to give it to him .
I 'm smelling weakness .
I 'm not being weak .
Then why talk to him ?
So I can just end this thing once and for all .
Well , that sounds convincing .
Come on , I got it .
The person you really should be talking to is Tiffany .
When are you heading over to the bonfire ?
Nice subject change . I 'm on my way now .
I wanna get a good seat before the jocks start streaking
like a pack of wild idiots .
Now you 're really making me sad I 'm missing it .
You want me to swing by first ?
No , it 's okay .
But give Bobby the number , all right ?
Don 't say I didn 't warn you . - Fine , I 've been warned .
Hello . - This is TTR Protection .
We just registered your alarm .
Is there an emergency , or do you need assistance ?
No , not at all . I 'm just the babysitter .
I think the maid set off the alarm .
May I have the password please ?
Password ? I only have a number .
I 'll have to check with the Mandrakises to confirm your identity .
What is your name ? - Jill Johnson .
Okay , Miss Johnson , Mrs. Mandrakis confirmed .
- Good night . - Thank you .
Hello .
Hello , is somebody there ?
Is everything okay ? We just got a call from the alarm company .
Everything 's fine . The alarm just went off .
I don 't know how many times I 've written the number down for Rosa .
Did it wake the kids ? - I don 't think so .
They 're still quiet . Do you want me to go check ?
No , no . Trust me , you 'd know if they were awake .
Okay . Well , good . Call if you need anything else .
Okay . Thank you .
Rosa .
Is everything okay ?
Are you still here ?
Hello .
Mandrakis residence .
Is everything okay ?
Dr. Mandrakis ?
Hello .
Hello . - Hey .
Who is this ? - What are you wearing ?
Combat boots and a parka , you jerk . Who is this ?
Bobby , is this you ?
Whoever this is , this isn 't funny .
Yeah , it is .
Assholes .
Hello .
My God , the look on your face . - What the hell are you doing here ?
Oh , my God . Could this house be more awesome ?
Tiffany , you don 't just do this to people . Why didn 't you call ?
I just did .
How did you get in ? - The garage door is open .
What ?
What 's the big deal ?
I 've been getting really weird prank phone calls all night .
So then don 't answer the phone . I 'm sure they have voice mail .
Well , maybe I 'm expecting a call . - From Bobby ?
What 's it to you ? - Oh , I don 't know .
Maybe because I 'm your best friend .
It 's a little hard to remember after what you did .
How many times do I have to say that I 'm sorry ? It was one kiss .
And besides , you know what tequila does to me .
Then don 't drink .
Fine , I 'll try . - Face it , Tiffany
you 've been crushing on Bobby ever since ninth grade .
Yeah , I have .
It 's because he asked me out first . I was with him for one day
when he spotted you .
I never got my kiss , so I figured I had it coming to me .
Now we 're even .
You know what ? That 's the lamest excuse I 've ever heard .
Jill , I 'm a bitch .
I know that , you know that , everybody knows that .
Let 's go do a truce shot .
I bet they have a killer bar . - You 're quitting , remember ?
Sherry , port . So , what about something real , people ?
Voila . Tequila .
Didn 't we just talk about you not drinking , Tiffany ?
You were serious ? - Okay . You gotta go
because I 'm babysitting .
Okay , fine .
But at least come with me to the bonfire , just for a couple of hours .
I mean , the kids are asleep , right ?
So you could just set the alarm and no one would ever know .
Kidding .
Bye . - Bye .
Call me .
Shit . Oh , shit .
Oh , God .
Oh , no . Come on .
Tiffany . Tiffany , come on .
This isn 't funny .
Tiffany ?
Hello .
Mandrakis residence .
Jill , is that you ? - Bobby . Bobby , are you there ?
Wait , move around . We 've got a bad connection .
- Jill . - Yeah , it 's me .
Listen , have you been calling me ?
Hold on .
Can you hear me ? Is that better ? - Yeah , it 's better . Listen ...
No one can get a signal up here . - Bobby , listen .
Have you been calling me here ? - What ?
I won 't get mad . I just need to know if you 've been calling .
Well , Cody pranked you , but I made him stop .
Just once ? - Yeah , I think so .
Bobby , listen , this is very important . I won 't get mad .
Has he called me more than once ?
I don 't know .
Hold on , let me check .
Hey , Cody .
Bobby ?
Are you still there ?
The person you are trying to reach is out of range .
Please try your call again ...
Tiffany , I know it 's you .
I can see your name on caller ID , genius .
This isn 't Tiffany .
Who is this ?
Cody ?
Who 's Cody ?
You better cut this out .
Hello .
Hello . - Scarlet , it 's me , Jill .
Jill . - Can you hear me ?
Barely . No one can get any service up here .
Yeah , I know . Listen ...
- Did Tiffany come up to talk to you ? - Yeah , she came by .
Did you kiss and make up ?
Jill ?
Scarlet ... - Are you there ?
The person you are trying to reach is out of range .
Please try your call ...
Hello , you 've reached Ben Johnson .
Sorry I missed your call . Please leave a message after the beep .
Dad
it 's Jill here . Can you call me at the Mandrakises ' when you have a chance ?
Okay ? Thanks .
Please leave me a detailed message
and I 'll return your call as soon as I can . Have a great day .
Hi , Mrs. Mandrakis . It 's me , Jill , calling .
Could you give me a call when you get a chance ?
But don 't ... Don 't worry , everything 's fine . Okay , thank you .
Il Cielo , how may I help you ?
Hi . Can I speak with Dr. Mandrakis , please ?
Dr. Mandrakis _ He left about 40 minutes ago .
That 's what I thought . Okay , thank you .
Operator . How may I direct your call ?
Can I speak with the police ?
Is this an emergency ? - Yes .
No . No , not really .
Would you like me to connect you ? - Yes , please . Thank you .
Elan Valley Police Department , Officer Burroughs .
How can I help you ? - I 've been getting weird phone calls
about every 15 minutes from a man . It 's starting to scare me .
An anonymous caller , miss ? - Yes .
Has he threatened you ? - No .
Has he been using obscene language ?
No . Sometimes he doesn 't even say anything .
He just keeps on calling . - There 's not much we can do
unless there 's a real threat .
Is the phone listed in your name ? - No , I 'm just the babysitter .
What 's your name ? - Jill Johnson .
Do you have friends that can come over , keep you company ?
No , they 're all at the bonfire . My school 's having
this big thing by the ...
I know . We have a couple units over there .
Sounds pretty wild .
Rosa 's car . - What 's that ?
The housekeeper . I thought she left , but I ... I guess she hasn 't .
There you go . You feel better with the two of you there ?
Actually , I feel pretty stupid .
There 's a lot of freaks out there . You were right to call .
If you need anything else , just call back .
I 'm here all night . Just ask for Officer Burroughs .
Officer Burroughs . - Take care , miss .
Thank you .
Rosa ?
Rosa .
Are you down there ?
Hello , this is Rosa . Please , leave a message .
Hello , this is Rosa . Please , leave a ...
Hello . - Have you checked the children ?
Hello . - How were the children ?
Elan Valley Police .
He can see me . - I 'm sorry .
It 's Jill , the girl who called before about the man who can ...
Tell me what 's going on . - He called me again .
What did he say ? - He 's out there . He 's outside . He 's ...
He 's watching me through the windows .
Did you see him ? - No , but I know he can see me .
- He knew when I went upstairs . - Okay . Take a deep breath .
Where 's the housekeeper ? - I ... I don 't know .
L ... I ... I saw her purse and the keys
but I ... I can 't find her . - Is the house locked up ?
Yes . - Alarm system ?
It 's on . - Okay .
You 're safe inside that house . If he wanted to break in ...
- ... he wouldn 't be calling you . - But he must want something .
Listen to me .
Miss , he 's just some asshole trying to hassle you .
There 's something we can do . - What ?
I can alert the phone company , so when he calls
we can try and trace the call .
I can also get my commander to authorize a GPS trace
if he 's calling from a cell phone .
Now , I got your number here . Can you verify the address _
I don 't ...
I don 't know . My dad brought me here . I ...
It 's ... Wait . Here . 3378 Old Mill Road .
I know where that is . Now , if he calls again
try to keep him on the line for 60 seconds ...
- ... so we can trace the call . - I can 't .
He doesn 't stay on the phone for more than a few seconds .
I 'll see if I can get a car out to you .
But if I do , it 's gonna take at least 20 minutes from the time of dispatch .
Think you 'll be okay until then _
Yes . - Good .
Now , I 'll be watching the phone line . Call me if you need to .
Okay . Thank you .
Hello .
It 's you , isn 't it ?
No , no , no . Wait , wait . Wait , don 't hang up .
If you keep on calling , must mean you wanna talk , right ?
Is it me you 're calling for ?
Are you calling for the Mandrakises ?
Damn it .
Guesthouse .
Hey , it 's Todd . I 'm not here . I 'm up at school .
And if you don 't have the number , then there 's probably a reason .
Hi , it 's Jill , the babysitter .
If you or Rosa are in there , could you please pick up
or come up to the house ?
Someone 's been calling , and I called the police .
I was wondering if you could come up and wait here with me until they come .
Todd ?
Hello ?
Todd .
Hey , it 's Todd . I 'm not here . I 'm up at school .
And if you don 't have the number , then there 's probably a reason .
It 's you , isn 't it ?
How did you get this number ?
How do you know I 'm in here ?
Did you see me out there ?
Why are you doing this to me ?
Sixty seconds . Got you .
You called the wrong phone line .
Rosa .
Rosa ?
It 's Jill .
Hello .
I know it 's you .
I 'm not gonna be here much longer .
Dr. Mandrakis and his wife are coming home soon .
Why won 't you answer me ?
I know you 're there . I can ... I can hear you breathing .
Is that what you wanted ?
To scare me ?
Because if that 's what you want , you can stop now
because it really worked .
But you don 't know who I am , or where I live .
And Dr. Mandrakis is gonna take me home
as soon as he gets here .
But maybe even the police will take me home .
Please , I mean , there has to be a reason why you keep on calling me .
I mean
if you 're not trying to scare me , what do you want ?
Your blood
all over me .
Rosa ?
Stop calling me , you sick ... - Jill ? Listen to me .
We traced the call . It 's coming from inside the house .
Do you hear me ? It 's coming from inside the house .
You need to get out of there right now . Jill ?
Oh , my God .
Come on . Okay .
Kids , come on .
I 'm Jill , the babysitter .
Here . Stay right here . Stay ... Stay here .
Get out . Go out that window right there .
No .
Please , no .
Get away . Go on .
Come back !
Kids .
It 's Jill .
Where are you ?
Come on . Come on .
Come on .
Please .
Come on . Oh , God .
Kids .
Come on .
There . Are you guys okay ?
Kids , come on . You okay ? Come on . Gotta go .
Come on , gotta go , gotta go .
Come on .
Jill ! Jill , it 's okay . You 're safe ! - Stop it ! No !
How you doing ?
Where is he ? - We 've got him .
He 's in that police car right over there .
In ankle cuffs , handcuffs .
Enough sedatives to kill a horse . We 're gonna take him to the hospital .
We 'll have four cops guarding him around the clock .
That 's not enough .
Take care , Jill .
- reporting to you from Elan Valley
where police have just apprehended a suspect ...
wanted in the murders of 15 people here .
a violent struggle with his intended victim ...
he 's linked to murders where women
were stalked and harassed for hours ...
- an elaborate game of cat-and-mouse .
Police are looking for links between victims . They were young women ...
most recent victim was in Burford County , 125 miles west ...
Elan Valley .
As of now , his identity remains a mystery .
Oh , my God ! No ! No !
He 's in the house ! He 's in the house ! - Look ... Look , listen to me .
No ! No ! He 's in the house , Dad ! He 's in the house !
He 's in the house ! No , you don 't understand !
No ! He 's in the house !
He 's in the house !